It says that I am offline
oh cool I am live
wonder if anyone is actually going to come to this
that's ok how I don't watch twitch enough to know like how people do this
go to my twitch oh here we go this is ok this is what I want
sweet
I got a whisper
I don't know what that means
alright so we are going to try this
we are going to try
do you guys know what SLAM is?
so
you want to both map an environment
and keep track of your location in it
so here is the video that we are going drive
you see this
it's a video of some guy driving on a road
and the idea is
can we figure out how that car is moving
and make a map of the environment that he is driving through at the same time
so there are opensource programs to do this
but we are going to try to code our own
how many people are watching right now
can I tell?
this is total views
this is not useful
cmon twitch
I don't know. I found this things really hard to use. Alright let's get started...
I have this little directory called
twitchslam
slam.py
so one of the things that we are going to do is
python 3
which
I have never really used before
so we are all here learning together... I will have to write print
with the parenthesis
so I have that file
there
test.mp4... we can see that it's like live
test.mp4
give it a few minutes I believe yea I don't understand
It's says that I am away... I am online
Can I change that?
I don't know like how many people are watching and I can see
this details
0 people watching now, ow interesting
14 people watching now, ok not bad
but yea so let's this is going to be slow
will take some time
load mp4 video, no no mp3 video
I am like google
so they use the cv2 video capture api
so like
with everything opencv what are the odds
that this is actually going to work
that doesn't work
like that
test.mp4
cv2 uses the same interface for
oh man this xkcd that I really like
not this one
oh this one, oh this one made me so happy
my mouse need to scroll the other way
alight so what I am going to do is I am going to put the
no no we are not working on supercruise I am going to put the twitches
over here
alright I actually have another monitor over here
so that's where the twitches are going you are not scopies you are twitches
ok cool
ret
frame
cap.read
if ret
is true
else break
process frame
frame
omg I can't trype